ILGWU Photographs 5780 P
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Local 99 [folder 1 of 3] (Box 22, Folder 6)
  includes: Women campaigning for Harriman and Roosevelt, October 18, 1954; Women addressing mini-sewing kits to be sent out; Election meeting at Manhattan Center where Manager Louis Dworkin was reelected, March 5, 1947 - the 22 and the star represents veteran Local 99 members who did not return from the war; Presentation to Louis Dworkin and Edward Kramer desk sets and plaques for their union efforts, presentation made by Chairman Harry Littman and Peter Fernandez; 4th of July Weekend at Unity House, Local 99 members celebrating holiday; Union reception after installation of Shelley Appleton as manager of Local 99 - David Dubinsky, Mr. and Mrs. Appleton, and Chairman of Local 99 Executive Board Harry Harrsesoffky; June 3, 1954 - Cloak and Suit Strike Action Committee Officers confer before meeting - Business Representatives Benjamin Laboda, Douglas Levin, and Nick Mule; Local 99 members pitching for help for WNET TV 13, the local educational Television station; Appleton congratulated by Stulberg after installation; Local 99 Executive Board - Shop Stewards and Committee members vote; June 3, 1954 Cloak and Suit Strike Action Committee, led by Representative Douglas Levin, votes to strike; January 15, 1960, Local 99 Contract signing; Stulberg signing an agreement; Local 99 Picket with Placards against Land-n-Sea Diplomat Spts (45 West 18th Street); Bellas Hess workers (Local 99) picketing with placards
- Local 99 [folder 2 of 3] (Box 22, Folder 7)
- Local 99 [folder 3 of 3] (Box 22, Folder 8)
- Local 102 [folder 1 of 2] (Box 22, Folder 9)
  includes: Local 102 signing 3 way contract, present at signing are: Sam Berger and Dave Karp of Local 102, Abe Schlesinger Union Attorney and Charles Zimmerman manager of Local 22, Trucker Employers and Association members; Crowd Scene at the Local 102 Annual Dance; Local 102 Boxing Team receiving trophy; Local 102 Voting in election *note - one of the few women members of Local 102 is holding ballot; Banquet scenes; Local 102 workers loading their trucks, placing election propaganda on the trucks; Stulberg leading agreement signing
- Local 102 [folder 2 of 2] (Box 22, Folder 10)
- Local 105 - selected (Box 22, Folder 11)
  includes: Shop scene - Asian man pressing garment; Shop Scene - Asian women sewing; Shop scene - Black woman sewing Union Label onto garments
- Local 105 [folder 1 of 7] (Box 22, Folder 12)
  includes: Banquet photos, Louis Stulberg speaking, Antonini and Local 105 Manager Martin Cohen on dais; Manager Martin Cohen presenting a check for $1000 for New York Cardiac Home to Samuel Le Savoy, President of the NY Cardiac Home, and Harry Hershfield looking on; Local 105 and the Employer Association giving aid to Refugees: George Karp, Sidney Cohen and Martin Cohen welcoming refugees, June 30, 1951; Local 105 outing at Unity House, June, 1953; Local 105 New Years Party, Hotel New Yorker, Martin Cohen and wife, and members; Local 105 13th Anniversary Dance - Joseph Freno, Martin Cohen, and Phil Kramer, Boston, Mass.; Official opening of Local 105 new Headquarters - William Peer, Martin Cohen, Burton Turkus; Martin Cohen and Employer Samuel Zemensky of Brookshire Sportswear Inc. distribute vacation checks to members, June 8, 1954; Navy annual dance with Local 105 gals, February 19, 1955; Receiving docks for American Israeli Supply Mission - Martin Cohen and others standing in front of large boxes of Women's Khaki Shirts ready to be shipped; David Dubinsky Speech; Members asking Manager Martin Cohen and Bernie Leiderman after a membership meeting where Cohen described their new contract, April 3, 1956; Agreement signing; Local 105 Parade float; Convention scene; Local 105 marching toward Atlantic City convention; Audience shot; District Attorney Frank Hogan with twin girls of Veronica Burich, shop chairlady and sewing machine operator, member of Local 105; Rally at the Lincoln Memorial in Washington DC; young boy handing out shopping bags picketing Judy Blouses; women preparing to hand out anti - Judy Bond Blouses bags and leaflets; Demonstration with placards against Judy Bond Blouses; Group photo of George Meany with lots of children; Shop scene - women at sewing machines with observers; Picket with placards to "End Segregation in Southern Howard Johnsons"; Picket in front of Horn and Hardart before representation election; Local 105 marching in a parade; Member of Local 519, Brunswick, Georgia in Jacksonville, Florida combining a Union Label Campaign and an anti-Judy Bond campaign; Anzio Frocks striker - demonstration with place card; Local 105 marching for "Full Equality and Human Dignity for All Americans NOW", demonstration with placards; Picket against Woolworths and their discrimination practices in the South; Local 22 members on White House (Washington DC) Lawn; Individual Photo of Herbert Lehman; Photo of award received by Martin Cohen from The Continental Society for Children of the Virgin Islands, Inc. - 1950 Award for his contribution to the Welfare of Underprivileged Children of the Virgin Islands and of New York City; Political press conferences; Martin Cohen with a child with Muscular Dystrophy; David Dubinsky signing an agreement; Robert F. Kennedy at Convention; Picket in front of Bloomingdale's
- Local 105 [folder 2 of 7] (Box 22, Folder 13)
- Local 105 [folder 3 of 7] (Box 22, Folder 14)
- Local 105 [folder 4 of 7] (Box 22, Folder 15)
- Local 105 [folder 5 of 7] (Box 22, Folder 16)
- Local 105 [folder 6 of 7] (Box 22, Folder 17)
- Local 105 [folder 7 of 7] (Box 22, Folder 18)
- Local 117 - selected (Box 22, Folder 19)
  includes: Meeting crowd scene - Unemployed members of Local 117 listening for information on disbursements they are to receive
- Local 117 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  includes: Press Luncheon - Ben Kaplan, Manager of Local 117 announces to press 1/2 Days pay for Welfare Relief; Portrait of Ben Kaplan; David Dubinsky Installing Kaplan as Manager of Local 117; Nat Windman, Asst. Manager of Local 117, putting hat on 70 year old member Bernard Fenster
- Local 142 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  includes: Eleanor Roosevelt sewing in the first Union Label in a scarf at a ceremony; Local 142 Manager Joseph Tuvim explaining the details of the new contract to a membership meeting; Local 142 manager Joseph Tuvim shown with VP Harry Greenberg receiving a citation from the National Committee for Rural Groups; Local 142 members distribute anti - Judy Bond leaflets outside Gimbel Brothers (Department Store); Tuvim shaking hands with Jacob Potofsky after being installed as a newly elected vice president of the Union Label and Service Trades Department of Greater New York, also present are Richard Walsh, Charles Garrahan, and Harry Avrutin
- Local 155 - selected (Box 22, Folder 22)
  includes: Local 155 of the Knitgoods Workers Union picketing James Knitting Mills Employees to join their union, Arthur Jacobson is the organizer picketing; Local 155 marching in a parade; happy Local 155 members surrounding Mayor LaGuardia after agreement was signed; Jack Wishnefsky and Max Kampelmacher picketing in front of Mar Jan and Sternberg Knit mills; Local 155 marching in the 1964 Labor Day Parade, with Placards calling for the release of 100,000 men in Cuban Jails; Louis Nelson, Manager of Local 155 greeting FDR. Jr. at Washington Irving High School, at Local 155 meeting
- Local 155 [folder 1 of 2] (Box 22, Folder 23)
  includes: Memorial for workers killed in the Triangle Shirtwaist Fire; a mother and her daughter sitting together thinking about the NAZI regime in Europe; Local 155 Workers Picketing in front of an Adolph's Trucking Trailer; Shop scene - Local 155 workers working in Knitting factory; Local 155 elections of 1974; Local 155 members and officers marching in the 1964 Labor Day Parade; Frederick Van And Residence - Flushing Avenue, north of Purdy Place, Bushwick, Brooklyn, NY, 1922; Louis Nelson, First Manager for Local 155, speaking during a meeting; Speech by Louis Nelson; Martin Cohen, manager of Local 105, presenting Assistant Manager George Karp a wrist watch for 15 Years of service, September 29, 1953; Local 155 meeting at Unity House; Picketers against Margaret Anzalone from Local 155 - demonstration with placards; Local 155 Installation, Roosevelt Hall, April 13, 1950; Local 155 Convention Delegates walking on the Atlantic City Boardwalk; Photo of the Local 155 Charter; Portrait of Louis Nelson
- Local 155 [folder 2 of 2] (Box 22, Folder 24)
- Local 155, elections 1971 [folder 1 of 3] (Box 22, Folder 25)
  includes: Photo of voting box; members preparing to vote - lined up at table; members in voting booths; people on the street outside voting area handing out leaflets; long line to get in to vote; campaign van with speakers on top and a poster on the side; membership meeting
- Local 155, elections 1971 [folder 2 of 3] (Box 22, Folder 26)
- Local 155, elections 1971 [folder 3 of 3] (Box 22, Folder 27)
- Local 226 - Springfield, MA (Box 22, Folder 28)
  includes: membership meeting; reception and banquet scenes
- London, Meyer - selected (Box 23, Folder 1)
  includes: Portrait; artist's sketch of Meyer London School
- London, Meyer (Box 23, Folder 2)
  Includes: David Dubinsky with Wagner and others at a dedication ceremony; Early London office scene
- Manhattan Lyceum - selected (Box 23, Folder 3)
  Includes: Front of the building
- Marshall, Louis (Box 23, Folder 4)
  Includes: portrait
- McCauley, James - selected (Box 23, Folder 5)
- McGovern - Shriver - selected (Box 23, Folder 6)
  Includes: crowd with placards; speech, Oct. 1972
- McGovern - Shriver (Box 23, Folder 7)
  Includes: George McGovern waving as he walks down the street; Eleanor McGovern shakes hands during a garment center tour, escorted by Murray Gross and Wilbur Daniels, Aug. 31, 1972; Eleanor McGovern welcomed by Murray Gross, Jack Hochman, Sol C. Chaikin, David Gingold, E. Howard Molisani, Evelyn Dubrow, Wilbur Daniels, and Abe Dolgen at the start of the garment district tour, Aug. 31, 1972. George McGovern - speech, Oct. 1972
- Management Engineering - selected (Box 23, Folder 8)
  Includes: Mitchell Lokiec with clipboard evaluates women operators at sewing machines, 1957, Sy Gris Shop; women at sewing machines being filmed for time motion studies, 1957
- Management Engineering [folder 1 of 2] (Box 23, Folder 9)
  Includes: banquet scenes in honor of William Gomberg; Luigi Morelli - speech; William Gomberg speech to CISL and UIL in Rome, Italy; a photo with Mr. Raia and W. McAdoo; McAdoo and Gomberg talking
- Management Engineering [folder 2 of 2] (Box 23, Folder 10)
- Matheson, Min (Lurye) (Box 23, Folder 10a)
  Includes: Portrait; A portrait of her husband; a banquet scene that includes both of them
- Matyas, Jennie - selected (Box 23, Folder 11)
  Includes: with David Dubinsky
- Matyas, Jennie (Box 23, Folder 11a)
  Includes Matyas speech addressing the Montreal Joint Board on stage with GEB
- May Day (Box 23, Folder 12)
  Includes: Demonstration in Union Square on May Day, 1937
- Meany, George - selected (Box 23, Folder 13)
  Includes: portrait; Meany with A. Philip Randolph; with David Dubinsky, Antonini, and Hochman
- Meany, George [folder 1 of 6] (Box 23, Folder 14)
  Includes: Meany speeches, 1957, 1965, 1972; with Eisenhower; with Goldberg in front of helicopter; press conference at Unity House; Mrs. Eugenia Meany sewing in ILG union label, June 1, 1961; at AFL-CIO convention, 1955; receiving award from David Dubinsky, Urban League Ex. Sec. Lester B. Granger, 1959; receiving "Forward" award from Stulberg - Paul Rubinstein, Simon Weber, Dr. Samuel Silverberg, Jacob T. Zukerman, also present, 1972; receiving Histadrut Award at Unity House June, 1961; Portrait, June 1961; with Philip Reuther, 1955; with Potofsky and David Dubinsky, 1959; with Goldberg; with Sol C. Chaikin; With Chaikin and wife; giving award to Stulberg, with Zimmerman, 1970; with Stulberg; with Henry Van Arsdale, 1961; with Chaikin and Sheinkman, 1977; with Joel Jacobson, Vincent J. Murphy at Merger Convention, 1961; talking with David Dubinsky, 1957; David Dubinsky and Meany playing cards
- Meany, George [folder 2 of 6] (Box 23, Folder 15)
- Meany, George [folder 3 of 6] (Box 23, Folder 16)
- Meany, George [folder 4 of 6] (Box 23, Folder 17)
- Meany, George [folder 5 of 6] (Box 23, Folder 18)
- Meany, George [folder 6 of 6] (Box 23, Folder 19)
- Miami, Florida - selected [folder 1 of 2] (Box 23, Folder 20)
  Includes: Demonstrators with placards, some in Spanish; man teaches an English class to Hispanic women; shop scene
- Miami, Florida - selected [folder 2 of 2] (Box 23, Folder 21)
- Miami, Florida [folder 1 of 9] (Box 23, Folder 22)
  Includes: A Portrait of Maria Serrano; Rally with Spanish and English placards and speeches; David Dubinsky speech at a banquet at the Dupont Plaza Hotel; A woman placing a tiara on the head of a beauty pageant winner wearing a Bennett Fashions ribbon; the pageant winner receives a watch from the Miami Joint Council Manager Robert Gladnick; Julia Rosario models a Daisy's Original dress; Group photos, Sept. 30, 1963; David Dubinsky speaking to group, Feb., 1964; women striking Cover Girl, Robbie Lynn Inc., Alvarez Fashions, Cheri's Fashions, Miss Jane, Randi - Robert Inc., Janet Junior's, and Monique Inc., Bennett Fashions, Inc., Miami Miss; Ermilda Hernandez of Smart Miss; Lucille Rodriguez of Mar - Cel Fashions; members of Local 415 with their hands raised; group photo of the Appeals Committee at the ILGWU Convention, May 6, 1971; advertisement for film on David Dubinsky; policeman talking to people in a crowd
- Miami, Florida [folder 2 of 9] (Box 23, Folder 23)
- Miami, Florida [folder 3 of 9] (Box 23, Folder 24)
- Miami, Florida [folder 4 of 9] (Box 23, Folder 25)
- Miami, Florida [folder 5 of 9] (Box 23, Folder 26)
- Miami, Florida [folder 6 of 9] (Box 23, Folder 27)
- Miami, Florida [folder 7 of 9] (Box 23, Folder 28)
- Miami, Florida [folder 8 of 9] (Box 23, Folder 29)
- Miami, Florida [folder 9 of 9] (Box 23, Folder 30)
- Miscellaneous - selected (Box 24, Folder 1)
  Includes: Chinese women working at Town East Garment Factory in Macao, around 1982; group shot of David Dubinsky, Jacob Potofsky, Harry Van Arsdale, A. Philip Randolph, and others; Man struggling with a young woman, trying to put her in the back of a police wagon; men getting coffee in a breadline; portrait of Harry Uviller; Tom Mooney and Warren Billings in front of jail bars; Pauline Newman, Eleanor Hewitt, and Rose Schneiderman talking; broadcast in 1934 from W.E.V.D.
- Miscellaneous (see also: Bx. 50 ff 13) [folder 1 of 10] (Box 24, Folder 2)
  Includes: David Dubinsky with Sec. of Agriculture Orville L. Freeman, April 27, 1962; Advertisement in New York Times to commemorate the 60th Anniversary of the ILGWU, June 23, 1960; Fernando de los Rios; group photo of John Wesley Jones, David Dubinsky, and George Meany; group photo of David Dubinsky, Meany, and others, at the Balboa Theater, Canal Zone, November 1956; women at jailhouse in bathing suits; Walter Reuther and other man, 1960; Man riding a stationary bicycle at Moss Rehabilitation Hospital in Philadelphia, March 28, 1969; Union members outside the Mass. State Labor Council Convention, 1967; strikers with placards, 1967; Newspaper clippings of police on horses in steel strike zone and John Fitzpatrick addressing the strikers; Group shots including Cahan, one was in 1936; David Dubinsky at reception for John Glenn; banquet scenes; Sen. Edmund Muskie, David Dubinsky, and Potofsky; Potofsky and David Dubinsky talking to Bayard Rustin at a banquet; ILGWU members in front of Christmas tree in Washington; children with Santa, 1980; portrait of Henry Schiff of Kuhn, Loeb and Co. Bankers, March 21, 1907; David Dubinsky leads members in voting with hands up; man signs to pledge support to United Nations; Portrait of Asian woman with child; black Montgomery marchers; ILGWU Convention, c. 1915; two young black children; David Dubinsky - speech; David Dubinsky with General Clark of the Army; crowd with placards supporting the hostages, Jan. 1980; George Meany - speech, Jun. 1975; Jim Mahoney, Roy T. Peraino, Gov. Milton Shapp, Sol C. Chaikin, Mayor Frank Rizzo, William Ross, and Richard McConnell at ground breaking ceremony in Philadelphia, Sept. 30, 1974; Muscular Dystrophy Association poster child looks at Horst Fisher, Ross Gredinger and Martin L. Cohen for her new coat; David Dubinsky puts a hat on the newest member of the ILGWU Health Brigade; David Dubinsky and Meany watch a cellist play; Jay Lovestone speaking; Trade Union Advisory Committee on International Affairs meeting, with David A. Morse, Lieut. Col. Ray L. Laux, Brig. Gen. George L. Eberle, A.E. Lyon, Thomas J. Harkins, Robert J. Watt, George Meany, David Dubinsky, Matthew Woll, Michael Ross, James B. Carey, and Clinton S. Golden; Korean girls knit with supplies donated by the ILGWU, March 15, 1967; portrait of Paul Douglas; portrait of Bayard Rustin, 1974; photo of a check to a woman for one dollar for two weeks wages; Meany with Stulberg, E. Howard Molisani; Garment Center in New York; Lady Bird Johnson, Adlai Stevenson, and David Dubinsky; Abraham Cahan speaking; Hubert Humphrey; rally with placards; picture of Potofsky, David Dubinsky, Wagner, and Goldberg; Chaikin and Liv Ullman; Meany speaking at Forand Bill Rally, 5/18/60; David Dubinsky with Ernest Bevin, Meany, 9/22/49; Angela Bambace; Charles Kreindler with others; Kreindler with Stulberg; LaGuardia swearing in magistrate as Cahan, David Dubinsky, and Antonini look on, 12/17/35
- Miscellaneous (see also: Bx. 50 ff 13) [folder 2 of 10] (Box 24, Folder 3)
- Miscellaneous (see also: Bx. 50 ff 13) [folder 3 of 10] (Box 24, Folder 4)
- Miscellaneous (see also: Bx. 50 ff 13) [folder 4 of 10] (Box 24, Folder 5)
- Miscellaneous (see also: Bx. 50 ff 13) [folder 5 of 10] (Box 24, Folder 6)
- Miscellaneous (see also: Bx. 50 ff 13) [folder 6 of 10] (Box 24, Folder 7)
- Miscellaneous (see also: Bx. 50 ff 13) [folder 7 of 10] (Box 24, Folder 8)
- Miscellaneous (see also: Bx. 50 ff 13) [folder 8 of 10] (Box 24, Folder 9)
- Miscellaneous (see also: Bx. 50 ff 13) [folder 9 of 10] (Box 24, Folder 10)
- Miscellaneous (see also: Bx. 50 ff 13) [folder 10 of 10] (Box 24, Folder 11)
- Mitchell, United States Secretary of Labor (Box 24, Folder 12)
  Includes: Mitchell and David Dubinsky
- Mobile Flood Unit - selected (Box 24, Folder 13)
  Includes: Mobile Health Center
- Mobile Flood Unit [folder 1 of 4] (Box 24, Folder 14)
  Includes: People standing in line for the Mobile Health Center, 1955, Pennsylvania; nurse giving a girl a shot, 1955; front of old New York Union Health Center at 17 Irving Place; New York Center; crowd scene with David Dubinsky speaking next to Mobile Health Center; Harlem children next to Mobile Health Center; Mobile Health Center being loaded onto a ship; David Dubinsky next to Mobile Health Center; aftermath of 1956 floods in Pennsylvania; ILGWU mobile health workers handing out food; nurses; flu shot at Penn State Mills, Allentown, Pennsylvania, Local 111; workers of the Marilyn Coat Co. line up for chest X-rays, July 1959; children line up outside Mobile Health Center; Mobile Health Center driving at night; Stulberg and Zimmerman in Mobile Health Center; Antonini, Julius Hochman, Jennie Matyas in front of Mobile Health Center; Hochman shaking hands in front of the Mobile Health Center
- Mobile Flood Unit [folder 2 of 4] (Box 24, Folder 15)
- Mobile Flood Unit [folder 3 of 4] (Box 24, Folder 16)
- Mobile Flood Unit [folder 4 of 4] (Box 24, Folder 17)
- Modigliani, Giuseppe Emanuele - selected (Box 24, Folder 18)
  Includes: Modigliani with David Dubinsky, Antonini, other at Madison Square Garden, Nov. 28, 1934; David Dubinsky gives a check to Modigliani; Modigliani - speech
- Modigliani, Giuseppe Emanuele (Box 24, Folder 19)
  Includes: Group shot that includes Modigliani, David Dubinsky, and Antonini; Modigliani and Antonini shaking hands; group shot with David Dubinsky, Modigliani, Antonini, Angela Bombace, 11/28/34
- Mondale, Walter (Box 24, Folder 20)
  Includes: Chaikin introducing Mondale to Henoch Mendelsund at a Banquet, 5/83
- Nagler, I. (Box 24, Folder 21)
  Includes: Dedication ceremony for Nagler Hall at F.I.T., Dec. 1, 1962; Woman winning Nagler Award, July, 1960
- National Board Coat and Suit Industry (Box 24, Folder 22)
  Includes: Women modeling coats for the American Coat and Suit Festival; David Dubinsky - speech; exhibits at the February 1969 meeting of the National Board of Coat and Suit Industry in Miami, Florida; David Dubinsky reads a copy of Justice that reports that he is retiring and that the G.E.B. elected Stulberg president, April 1966; first Annual Convention of the National Coat and Suit Industry Recovery Board, Washington DC, June 1936, includes David Dubinsky; R. V. Ingersoll, David Dubinsky, A.J. Altmeyer, I. Feinberg, and J.J. Walker, 1944; meeting of enforcement officers, Coat and Suit Code Authority, April, 1934; Board of Trustees of the Retirement Fund of the Coat and Suit Industry, David Dubinsky, and Stulberg
- National Recovery Administration - selected (Box 24, Folder 23)
  Includes: Byres H. Gitchell, Frances Perkins, and David Dubinsky, Jan 22, 1934, at official inauguration of NRA label in dress industry
- Needle Trades High School (Box 24, Folder 24)
  Includes: David Dubinsky speaking at dedication of Needle Trades High School; LaGuardia, David Dubinsky, and workers with the cornerstone at the dedication
- Negotiations - selected (Box 24, Folder 25)
  Includes: David Dubinsky with Hochman, LaGuardia, and others
- Negotiations [folder 1 of 3] (Box 25, Folder 1)
  Includes: David Dubinsky, Hochman, Zimmerman, Antonini, LaGuardia; David Dubinsky on July 11, 1935; July 15, 1937; women representing Little Prince, Columbia and Windsor, and Mart Realty Corporation; David Dubinsky shakes hands with Isidore A. Agree as William O'Dwyer looks on; Stulberg and Zimmerman talking; David Dubinsky in the Bobbie Brooks negotiations, 2/64; Chaikin, Wilbur Daniels, and David Gingold at the Leslie Fay negotiations, Feb. 1973; David Dubinsky, Herbert H. Lehman, Harry Uviller, and Louis Rubin; Antonini, Uviller, Stulberg, Zimmerman and representatives of Popular Priced Dress Manufacturers' Group, Feb. 1967; Louis Rubin, Harry Uviller, Mayor Wagner, former Gov. Lehman, and David Dubinsky, March 13, 1958; Members of Local 114 ratifying their new contract, April 28, 1966; negotiating committee for G.C. Bing, Town Creek, Alabama; Angela Bambace and William Sagel, 1969; Bobbie Brooks negotiations, December, 1964; David Dubinsky, Hochman, and Zimmerman, 1946; Chaikin at Cloak Signing, 4/80; David Dubinsky at negotiations, 1965
- Negotiations [folder 2 of 3] (Box 25, Folder 2)
- Negotiations [folder 3 of 3] (Box 25, Folder 3)
- Newman, Pauline - selected (Box 25, Folder 4)
  Includes: Portraits, 1965 and others. - See also: 5780/069 - Box 2
- Newman, Pauline (Box 25, Folder 5)
  Includes: negative of her portrait
- New Jersey - selected (Box 25, Folder 6)
  Includes: Women strikers with placards
- New Jersey (Box 25, Folder 7)
  Includes: Rally for Carter and Mondale, Union City, 1980; Democratic rally, 1981; James Florio, 1981
- New York Cloak Joint Board - selected (Box 25, Folder 8)
  Includes: Strikers with placards, July 29, 1952; Israel Feinberg, James Farrell, and Bernard Englander
- New York Cloak Joint Board [folder 1 of 9] (Box 25, Folder 9)